import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

class About5 {
  final String question;
  final String answer;
  About5({@required this.question, @required this.answer});
}
String string="No Name";
List<About5> names = [
  About5(
      question: "ACM",
      answer: "Association for Computing Machinery"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "AI",
      answer: "Artificial Intelligence"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ALGOL",
      answer: "Algorithic Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ALU",
      answer: "Arithmetic Logic Unit"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "A/D",
      answer: "Analog-to-Digital"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ABC",
      answer: "Atanasoff Berry Computer"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "AMD",
      answer: "Advanced Micro Devices"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ARPANET",
      answer: "Advanced Research Project Agency Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ASCII",
      answer: "American Standard Code for Information Interchange"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "BASIC",
      answer: "Beginners All-purpose Symbolic Instruction Code"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "BCD",
      answer: "Binary Coded Decimal"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "BIOS",
      answer: "Basic Inpute Output System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "BIPS",
      answer: "Billions of Instructions Per Second"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "BPI",
      answer: "Bytes Per Inch"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CAD",
      answer: "Computer Aided Design"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CAE",
      answer: "Computer Aided Engineering"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CAN",
      answer: "Campus Area Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CASE",
      answer: "Computer Aided Software Engineering"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CD",
      answer: "Compact Disk"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CDC",
      answer: "Control Data Corporation"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CD-R",
      answer: "CD-Recordable"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CD-ROM",
      answer: "Compact Disk Read Only Memory"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CD-RW",
      answer: "CD Read/Write"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CL",
      answer: "Command Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CLI",
      answer: "Command Line Interface"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "COBOL",
      answer: "Common Business Oriented"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CODASYL",
      answer: "Conference On Data Systems"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CPU",
      answer: "Central Processing Unit"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "CRT",
      answer: "Cathode Ray Tube"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "D/A",
      answer: "Digital-to-Analog"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DAT",
      answer: "Digital Audio Tape"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DBMS",
      answer: "Data Base Management System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DBS",
      answer: "Demand Based Switching"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DDL",
      answer: "Data Definition Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DDS",
      answer: "Digital Data Storage"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DEC",
      answer: "Digital Equipment Corporation"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DMA",
      answer: "Direct Memory Access"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DNA",
      answer: "Digital Network Architecture"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DPI",
      answer: "Dots Per Inch"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DRAM",
      answer: "Dynamic RAM"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DSN",
      answer: "Distributed Systems Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DTS",
      answer: "Digital Theater System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "DVD",
      answer: "Digital Video/Versatile Disk"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "EBCDIC",
      answer: "Extended Binary Coded Decimal Interchange Code"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "EDSAC",
      answer: "Electronic Delay Storage Automatic Calculator"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "EDVAC",
      answer: "Electronic Discrete Variable Automatic Calculator"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "EFM",
      answer: "Eight-to-Fourteen Modulation"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ENIAC",
      answer: "Electronic Numerical Integrator And Calculator"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "EPG",
      answer: "Electronic Programming Guide"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "EPIC",
      answer: "Explicitly Parallel Instruction Computing"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "EPROM",
      answer: "Erasable Programmable Read-Only Memory"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FAT",
      answer: "File Allocation Table"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FDM",
      answer: "Frequency Division Multiplexing"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FEP",
      answer: "Front End Processor"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FLOPS",
      answer: "Floating Point Operations Per Second"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FM",
      answer: "Frequency Modulation"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FMS",
      answer: "File Management System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FORTRAN",
      answer: "FORmula TRANslation"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FSK",
      answer: "Frequency Shift Keying"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "FTP",
      answer: "File Transfer Protocol"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "GB",
      answer: "Giga Bytes"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "GFLOPS",
      answer: "Giga FLOPS"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "GHz",
      answer: "Giga Hertz"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "GNU",
      answer: "Gnu Not Unix"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "GPRS",
      answer: "General Packet Radio Service"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "GSM",
      answer: "Global System for Mobile communication"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "GUI",
      answer: "Graphical User Interface"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "HP",
      answer: "Hewlett Packard"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "HSS",
      answer: "Hierarchical Storage System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "HTML",
      answer: "HyperText Markup Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "HTTP",
      answer: "HyperText Transport Protocol"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "IBM",
      answer: "International Business Machine"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "IC",
      answer: "Integrated Circuit"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "IDN",
      answer: "Integrated Digital Networks"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "IP",
      answer: "Internet Protocol"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "IrDA",
      answer: "Infrared Data Association"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ISDN",
      answer: "Integrated Services Digital Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ISP",
      answer: "Internet Service Provider"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "JPEG",
      answer: "Joint Photographic Experts Group"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "JRE",
      answer: "Java Runtime Engine"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "JSP",
      answer: "Java Server Pages"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "LAN",
      answer: "KLocal Area Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "LCD",
      answer: "Liquid Crystal Display"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "LED",
      answer: "Light Emitting Diode"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "LPM",
      answer: "Line Per Minute"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "LSI",
      answer: "Large Scael Integration"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MAN",
      answer: "Metropolitan Area Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MAR",
      answer: "Memory Address Register"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MB",
      answer: "Mega Bytes"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MBR",
      answer: "Memory Buffer Register "
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MIDI",
      answer: "Musical Instrument Digital Interface"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MIPS",
      answer: "Millions of Instructions Per Second"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MNP",
      answer: "Microcom Network Protocol"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MPEG",
      answer: "Moving Pictures Experts Group"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MS-DOS",
      answer: "MicroSoft Disk Operating System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "MVT",
      answer: "Multiprogramming with Variable Tasks"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "NIC",
      answer: "Network Interface Card"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "NICNET",
      answer: "National Informatics Center NETwork"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "NOS",
      answer: "Network Operating System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "OCR",
      answer: "Optical Character Recognition"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "OMR",
      answer: "Optical Mark Reader"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "OS",
      answer: "Operating System"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "OSI",
      answer: "Open System Interconnection"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "OSS",
      answer: "Open Source Software"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "PAN",
      answer: "Personal Area Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "PDF",
      answer: "Portable Document Format"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "PDL",
      answer: "Program Design Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "PDP",
      answer: "Program Data Processor"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "PIP",
      answer: "Peripheral Interchange Program"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "PROM",
      answer: "Programmable Read-Only Memory"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "QOS",
      answer: "Quality of Service"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "RAM",
      answer: "Random Access Memory"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ROM",
      answer: "Read Only Memory"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SDLC",
      answer: "Software Development Life Cycle"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SEQUEL",
      answer: "Structured English QUEry Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SGML",
      answer: "Syntax for Generalized Markup Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SIMM",
      answer: "Single In-line Memory Module"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SNA",
      answer: "Systems Network Architecture"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SNOBOL",
      answer: "StriNg Oriented and symBOlic Language"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SRAM",
      answer: "Static RAM"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "SSI",
      answer: "Small Scale Integration"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "TCP",
      answer: "Transport Control Protocol"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "TDM",
      answer: "Time Division Multiplexing"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "UDP",
      answer: "User Datagram Protocol"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "ULSI",
      answer: "Ultra Large Scale Integration"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "UPC",
      answer: "Universal Product Code"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "URL",
      answer: "Uniform Resource Locator"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "USB",
      answer: "Universal Serial Bus"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "VAN",
      answer: "Value Added Network"
  ),
  About5(
      question: "VCR",
      answer: "Video Cassette Recorder"
  ),

];